<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-15T19:05:24-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Millennial</title><subtitle>a minimalist Jekyll theme for running a blog or publication</subtitle><author><name>Paul Le</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hey there!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/about-the-author" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hey there!" /><published>2024-02-14T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2024-02-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/about-the-author</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/about-the-author">&lt;p&gt;My name is Jessie. I’m someone who loves exploring new horizons, both in the tech world and in everyday life. Born in a small town in China and now living in Canada, my journey has taken me from studying chemical engineering to diving deep into computer science. My goal? To drive digital transformation, help others embrace and integrate the latest technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But life isn’t all about work for me. After the computers are off, you can find me on my yoga mat. Yep, I’m also a certified yoga teacher. This helps me stay balanced and open to all the amazing cultures our world has to offer. I’m always up for trying new things, whether it’s a new food, a new book, or a new hobby. My life motto is pretty simple: ‘I’ll try anything once.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, whether we’re talking about the latest in digital tech or figuring out a new yoga pose, I’m all about mixing the old with the new. If you’re into chatting about how technology can change our lives or just looking for someone to try out a new restaurant with, I’m here. Let’s see what new adventures we can find together!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jessie Wang</name></author><category term="facts" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">My name is Jessie. I’m someone who loves exploring new horizons, both in the tech world and in everyday life. Born in a small town in China and now living in Canada, my journey has taken me from studying chemical engineering to diving deep into computer science. My goal? To drive digital transformation, help others embrace and integrate the latest technology.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/snow.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/snow.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Projects</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/personal-projects" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Projects" /><published>2024-02-13T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2024-02-13T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/personal-projects</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/personal-projects">&lt;p&gt;These projects primarily serve as vehicles for self-education and enjoyment, rather than being highly sophisticated endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vr-application-for-google-cardboard&quot;&gt;VR Application for Google Cardboard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project involves developing a VR application specifically tailored for Google Cardboard, a low-cost VR platform. The application offers users immersive experiences in a fictional world. Through interactive elements, users can explore and engage with the virtual environment. The goal is to provide an accessible and engaging VR experience for educational and entertainment purposes using smartphones and a basic cardboard viewer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0zzSVJO7e-8?si=maQVlErfGa0mcTpp&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;unity-faceware&quot;&gt;Unity Faceware&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Live tracking facial expression using Unity Faceware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GaGvRJp015g?si=0wjfXLyRYd7lA_Ri&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;edmonton-pothole-detection-using-dashcam&quot;&gt;Edmonton Pothole Detection using Dashcam&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project aims to develop a system that utilizes dashcam footage to detect and analyze potholes on road surfaces. By leveraging computer vision techniques, the system will identify potential potholes from video data captured by the dashcam. Through image processing and machine learning algorithms, it will differentiate between road imperfections and actual potholes, accurately identifying their locations and severity. The system’s output can be used to generate real-time alerts for drivers, municipalities, or road maintenance authorities, enabling timely repairs and improving road safety.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/pothole_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Pothole Detection Result&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;movie-recommendation-website&quot;&gt;Movie Recommendation Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project involves creating a user-friendly website for movie recommendations by leveraging the IMDb database. The website will allow users to search for movies, explore detailed information such as plot summaries, cast, and ratings sourced from IMDb. Utilizing collaborative filtering or content-based recommendation algorithms, the website will offer personalized movie recommendations based on users’ preferences and viewing history. Users can also rate movies, add them to watchlists, and share recommendations with others. The goal is to provide an intuitive platform for movie enthusiasts to discover new films and enhance their movie-watching experience based on IMDb’s extensive database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website is inactive now due to high maitenance cost.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jessie Wang</name></author><category term="resources" /><category term="documentation" /><category term="sample" /><summary type="html">These projects primarily serve as vehicles for self-education and enjoyment, rather than being highly sophisticated endeavors.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/founder_tree.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/founder_tree.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>